A Guide to the Papers of Robert Frost, 1873-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III. Miscellaneous
  - P. E. N. News, Vol. IX, No. 5, devoted to the memory of Robert Frost, 1963 April; Copy, 3 p. (Box 11)
  - The California Friends of Robert Frost: Luncheon commenorating the ninetieth anniversary of the birth of Robert Frost; last page reproduces the first appearance of the poem, "Once by the Pacific" [three copies], 1964 March 26; Program (Box 11)
  - Poem, "An Empty Threat" [two copies], 1971; Mimeo (Box 11)
  - First day covers of the centennial of Robert Frost's birth, from Plymouth State College, 1974 May 26; Brochures (Box 11)
  - The Plymouth State College Alumni Association: Presentation of the seventh Frost Contemporary American Award to Dr. James Duane Squires, 1979 April 23; Program (Box 11)
  - The Poetry Society: Announcement of Robert Frost lectures and poetry readings in Great Britain, Broadside (Box 11)
  - Invitations and Programs pertaining to Robert Frost lectures and poetry readings, greeting cards bearing Frost quotations, and miscellaneous matrial, 1952-1979; Printed (Box 11)
  - St. Patrick's Greetings, to Robert Frost and family to "Try to help dear old Erin--by word and sympathy," speaking of Erin Go Bragh. Two cards: "Erin Go Bragh" and "St. Patrick's Greetings. A Wish to dear old Erin that freedom's day is near", [1912-1913]; Cards (Box 11)
- Prints -- Drawings and Sketches
  - Two pencil drawings by Robert Frost with his notes, entitled "Three Acre Desideratum" and "Potato Patch", [ca. 1912]; Drawings (Box 11)
  - "The Sound of the Trees' Robert Frost" by E. A. Anderson, oil on board [UVa Art Index #637], Painting
  - Child's booklet, "Papa Christmas 1910," of drawings, 1910 [December 25]; Drawings (Box 11)
- Printed
  - "Robert Frost Awarded Limited Editions Club Medal," Publishers' Weekly, 1949 November 26; Printed (Box 11)
  - Reviews of The Daffodil Fields (1913) by John Masefield and North of Boston (1914) by Robert Frost, [1913-1914]; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Newspaper clippings about Robert Frost and related topics, including the Clifton Waller Barrett Library, [ca. 1925-1960]; 10 items (Box 11)
  - Article, "A Most Lamentable Comedy" by Grant Showeman, in School & Society, with explanatory note written at top of first page by Robert Frost, 1931 April 11; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Magazine and newspaper clippings about Robert Frost and his works, 1915-1963; Printed (Box 11)
  - Map of Derry, New Hampshire, the Site and Travels in the Vicinity of Robert Frost's Farm, 1969; Printed (Box 11)
  - Newspaper clippings re the Robert Frost commemorative postage stamp and Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1974; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Magazine and newspaper clippings about Robert Frost, 1950-1979; Printed (Box 11)
  - Chicago, Rock Island & Pacific Railroadand County Map of Iowa, [1872]; Printed (Box 11)
  - "A Poet Recognized" by David Tatham, a pamphlet concerning Robert Frost's stay in England, 1912-1915, 1970; Printed (Box 11)
  - "The Struggle to Create a University" by Clifton Waller Barrett, 1973 April 13; Printed (Box 11)
  - The Journal of Modern Literature, containing an article by Lesley Lee Francis, "Robert Frost and the Majesty of Stones Upon Stones", 1981; Printed (Box 11)
- Recordings
  - "Derry Down Derry," reading of Robert Frost poems by Lesley Frost Ballantine, 1966; Phonograph (Box P-559)
  - Recording of "An Old Man's Winter Night," "The Runaway," and "A Soldier" by Robert Frost at the home of Charles H. Foster, Iowa City, Iowa, 1938; Metal phonodisk (Box P-614)
  - Recording of "Stopping By Woods on a Snowy Evening," "Desert Places," and "A Leaf Treader" by Robert Frost at the home of Charles H. Foster, Iowa City, Iowa, 1938; Metal phonodisk (Box P-615)
  - Recording of the "Robert Frost Memorial Services" narrated by Allen Tate, 1963; Reel-to-reel (Box T-841)
- Photographs
  - Robert Frost, head and shoulders, left profile, Photograph
  - Robert Frost, head and shoulders, seated, with hands clasped, with another pose of Frost [at the same time], Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated at a small table, facing front, with left elbow propped on table and head resting on left hand. Signed by Frost. Photograph by Edward Sweetland, White House Studio, [ca. 1915]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated sideways in straight chair, facing front, with arm resting on back of chair, [ca. 1915]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated at desk [Morris chair with board resting on chair arms], writing, in Franconia, Amherst, New Hampshire, [ca. 1915]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated at desk [Morris chair with board resting on chair arms], writing, and facing front, in Franconia, Amherst, New Hampshire. Wide angle view of above photograph, [ca. 1915]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost with his daughter, Lesley Frost Ballantine in the background, and her children, Lee and Elinor, and their Airedale, Ricky in the foreground. Photograph by Jacob Lofman, Photograph
  - Robert Frost, standing, left hand in jacket pocket, in front of unidentified building, Photograph
  - Robert Frost, as an elderly man, standing beside a horse with his arms around the horse's neck, Photograph
  - Robert Frost as a young man, head and shoulders, facing front, Photograph
  - Robert Frost as a young man, standing, wearing an overcoat, Photograph
  - Henry Holt and Company publicity photograph of Robert Frost "author of 'West Running Brook.'", 1928
  - Robert Frost, standing, facing front, at the Lake Placid Club, New York, 1957; Photograph
  - Robert Frost shaking hands with Clifton Waller Barrett at the Lake Placid Club [two copies], 1957; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, standing, hands in jacket pockets, at Camp Cavendish [in color], 1957; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, standing facing side, at Camp Cavendish [in color], 1957; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, standing and talking and smiling with hands spread, at Camp Cavendish [in color], 1957; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, head and shoulders -- photograph by Joe Clark, 1962 November 13; Photograph
  - Robert Frost-- portrait etched by Richard Hood, signed by the artist and by Frost, Engraving
  - House connected with Robert Frost-- color photograph by Wilson Color, Bellows Falls, Vermont, n.d.; Photograph
  - Metal plaque by Sedgwick, 1964; Plaque (Box Mini Tray 1)
    Obverse: Head of Robert Frost with legend "1874 Robert Lee Frost 1962." Reverse: "California Friends of Robert Frost/Born/San Francisco/March 26, 1874/Newspaper Boy/Bobbin Boy/Teacher/Journalist/Farmer/Poet/Died, Boston, Mass./January. 29, 1963"
  - Obverse side of plaque, [1964]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated, hands in lap, inscribed by Frost "To North of Boston's northmost friend Mathias Hayin", Photograph
  - Robert Frost in Franconia, Amherst, [ca. 1915]; Photograph
    Caption: Robert Frost about 1915. From Robert Frost and John Bartlett: The Record of a Friendship by Margaret B. Anderson, Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc.
  - Robert Frost class photograph at 7-8 years, n.d.; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated, inscribed "to J. L. Ingraham with best wishes" and signed by Frost. Printed, Photograph
  - Robert Frost as an infant, n.d.; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, head and shoulders, seated at a small table, facing front, with left elbow propped on table and head resting on left hand. Upper portion of photo by Edward Sweetland, White House Studio, Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated at desk [Morris chair with board across arm chairs], writing, in Franconia, Amherst, New Hampshire, [ca. 1915]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost and Elinor Frost, standing outside, in Plymouth, New Hampshire, [ca. 1912]; Photograph
  - Robert Frost, standing behind chair, in Franconia, Amherst, New Hampshire, Photograph
  - William Prescott Frost, head and shoulders, Photograph
  - Isabelle Moodie Frost, head and shoulders, Photograph
  - Elinor Frost, head and shoulders, Photograph
  - Elinor Frost, profile, n.d.; Photograph
  - Elinor Frost, profile, n.d.; Photograph
  - Elinor Frost, seated, with dog, at campsite, n.d.; Photograph
  - Lesley, Carol, Marjorie, and Irma Frost, standing, Photograph
  - Robert Frost and Elinor Frost with their young children and a pony, at Lynch Farm, [ca. 1908]; Photograph
  - Elinor Frost and Robert Frost standing, with children seated in front, outdoors with house in background, Photograph
  - Carol Frost as young man, standing, front, outside, Photograph
  - Will [ ], son-in-law of Frost with his daughter Robin, n.d.; Photograph
  - Isbelle Moodie Frost with her students, 1893; Photograph
  - Prescott Frost[?], head and shoulders, Photograph
  - Frost homestead, Derry, New Hampshire, 1907; Photograph
  - "Little Iddens," The Leadington, Dymock, England, Photograph
  - Premier Hotel, Russell Square, London, England, Photograph
  - House in Lawrence, Massachusetts, once inhabited by Robert Frost, n.d.; Photograph
  - Lawrence, Massachusetts High School, where Robert Frost began writing poetry as a student, n.d.; Photograph
  - Robert Frost exhibition of books featuring copies No. 1 of limited editions inscribed to Elinor Frost, ca. 1969; 7 items
  - Painting of Robert Frost mounted over the memorabilia in the Robert Frost Room of the Jones Library during dedication ceremonies during Amherst's bicentennial week in October, 1959, 1959 October; Photograph
  - Painting of Robert Frost mounted over the memorabilia in the Robert Frost Room of the Jones Library during dedication ceremonies during Amherst's bicentennial week in October, 1959. This picture was taken by Everett Kosarick, 1976 December; Photograph
  - [Plymouth Normal School] basketball team, 1912; 3 photos
  - "Little Iddens," The Leadington, Dymock, one of the residences of Robert Frost during his stay in England during 1912-1915, Photograph
  - Premier Hotel in Russell Square, London [black-and-white], 2 photos
  - Unidentified girl, head and shoulders, photographed by C. D. Crooke of Edinburgh [black-and-white], Photograph
  - Robert Frost taken at the podium of the New York Lake Placid Club during a visit with Mr. and Mrs. Clifton Waller Barrett [black-and-white], Photograph
  - Robert Frost, seated outdoors, right profile, inscribed "Robert Frost to William Stanley Braithwaite in friendship 1958", Photograph